

Bachelor in Computer Science, Assistant Research Scientist

I am an Assistant Research Scientist in the Security and Trust unit at FBK. I joined the S&T unit to explore and improve TLS analysis and delve into identity management. I am working concurrently between FBK and the Istituto Poligrafico e Zecca dello Stato.

Experiences

Fondazione Bruno Kessler (Trento, Italy)

Assistant Research Scientist • Feb., 2021 - Present

Security analysis of the TLS deployments of IPZS projects, TLS Analysis in Android Apps and TLS tool enhancement within the Security & Trust research unit.

Internship • *Feb, 2020 - May, 2020*

Study and improvement of TLS analysis tools within the Security & Trust research unit.

Projects

TLSAssistant

Version 1.3 and 2.0 (soon) • 2020 - Present

Fully-featured tool that combines state-of-the-art TLS analyzers with a report system that suggests appropriate mitigations and shows the full set of viable attacks.

iHash

Perceptual hashing library in python • 2020 - Present

Python library to easily check if two images are similar without machine learning by using Perceptual Hashing (phash and whash combined), with ban and unban image system.

Minor Works

Mallodroid

Conversion in Python 3 and enhancements • 2020 - 2021

telegram-deep-fakes-bot

Easy implementation and use of the first order model • 2020

<u>Rappresentanti Bot</u>

HelpDesk Telegram bot to support DISI Students in University of Trento ● 2019

Education

University of Trento (Trento, Italy)

Bachelor of Computer Science • Sept, 2017 - Mar, 2021

Thesis in TLS Analyzers for Android Apps - State-of-the-art Analysis and Integration in TLSAssistant

I.I.S. Primo Levi (Badia Polesine, Italy)

High School Diploma • Sept, 2012 - Sept, 2017

Final elaborate in *The psychoanalysis of James Joyce and the artificial intelligences*

Certifications

First Certificate

Cambridge Assessment English - B2 ● Apr, 2017

ECDL Base

ECDL / ICDL Certification • May, 2016

